A Guide to the Records of the Office of Academic Affairs, 1961-1977 (bulk 1965-1976)
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series VII: Records and Correspondence, 1969-1970
  - Subseries I: Extension and Research Division, 1969-1970
    - Transportation Consortium, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Union for Research and Experimentation in Higher Education, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - USAID Program, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Universities Research Association Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Upward Bound (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 28-29)
    - Virginia Legislative Internship Program, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - VPI University Center, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - VPI Industry Center at Rocky Mount, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Water Resources Center, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Westmoreland David Memorial Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - White House Fellowships, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Subseries J: General Correspondence, Reports, and Papers, A-Z, 1969-1970
    - ABC Board Hearing, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Internships, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Admission and Records, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - African American History Course, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Conference, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Alice, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Allotment, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - American Administration Internship Program, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - American Association of Higher Education, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - American Association of University Women, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - American Council on Education, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - American Men of Science, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Athletic Association, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Audio-Visual Resources (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 16-17)
    - Baily Research Grant, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Blacksburg Chamber Music Series, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Blacksburg-Christiansburg Water Authority, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Board of Visitors, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Committee, Building, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Bus Service, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Campus Disorder - Disciplinary Action (5 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 25-29)
    - Campus Governance Program, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Center for Continuing Education, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Choral Music Organization, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Chronicle for Higher Education, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Cincinnati Society, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Civilian Honor Court, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights Compliance, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Classified Personnel, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Citizens for Communal Development, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - College Entrance Examination Board, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Commencement, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Commission Research and Graduate Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Student Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Commission on Undergraduate Studies - Subcommittees I, II, III, IV, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Commission on Undergraduate Studies (3 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 11-13)
    - Community College Coordinating Council Liaison, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Computer Committee Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Constitutional Revisions, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Committee Activity Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Community College Program, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Computer Center (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
    - Confederate Flag and "Dixie" in the Coliseum, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Consulting Policies, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Constitution and By Laws for Campus Organizations, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Corps of Cadets, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Council of Colleges of Arts & Sciences Membership Meeting, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Council of Deans, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Counseling Center, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Crockett, Miss Lucy H., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Daily Bulletin, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Danforth Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Dean, College of Education, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Deans' Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Deans' Meetings - Miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Maintaining files of Negro applicants considered for Teaching Positions, 1969
    - Deans of Men and Women's Programs, Dean for Student Services, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Derring Hall - Physical Plant Plan, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Diplomat-in-Residence, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Education, College of, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Education TV, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Engineering, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Education and World Affairs, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Enrollment Data, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Executive Vice President McKeefery Correspondence, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Extramural Funding, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Evaluation, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Handbooks (other colleges and universities), 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Publications, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Minutes - Faculty Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Fellowships, Special Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - 5-Day Week, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Furniture, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Fraternity/Sorority Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Grade Summary Report, Fall, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Graduate School, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Graduate Teaching Assistant and Graduate Research Assistant Information, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Hahn, T.M President, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Higher Education and National Affairs Bulletin, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Holidays and Vacations, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Homecoming, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Cadet Honor Code, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Interdormitory Council, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Regional Council for International Education, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - International Programs, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - International Students, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - International Studies Program, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Liberty Bowl, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Leaves - Educational, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Ledgers, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Library Acquisition, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Library Allocation, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Library Annual Report, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Library Candidates, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Library Committee Minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Library Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Living- Learning Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - MAELSTROM (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Master's Degree Thesis Option, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Montgomery County Committee on Alcoholism, Crime and Poverty and Montgomery County Improvement Council, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Name Change - VPI, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - NASULGC, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - NCURA, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - National Science Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - NSF Center of Excellence Proposal, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Office of Institutional Research, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Orientation Committee (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 21-22)
    - Orientation, New Faculty, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Pass- Fail Information, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Committee, Patent, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Peace Corps, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Personal Director, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Placement Office, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Planning Session, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Postage, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Poverty and Development in Appalachia, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - President's Report, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - President's Staff Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Print Shop, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Religious Affairs - Proposal for a Crisis Center, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Regional Education Laboratory for the Carolinas and Virginia (RELVC) (4 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 36, Box 13, Folder 1-3)
    - Requisitions Office, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Saunders, Thomas J., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Showalter Memorial Hospital, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Southeastern Psychological Association (SEPA), 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Summer School, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Supplies Equipment, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - State of Virginia - Student Aid, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Student Activities Committee (2 folders), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
    - Student Center, Squires Hall (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
    - Student Disciplinary Action, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Student Forums Board, Student Government Association (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
    - Student Government Association, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Student Health Services, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Student Housing, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Student Leaders Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Student Leadership Committee, Student Life Policies, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Study Abroad Program, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4A)
    - Study Abroad Program - General Committee (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
    - Summer Stock Theatre Proposal, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Tech Festival, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Tech Woman, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Telephone, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Terminal Interviews, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - TIAA CREF, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Traffic Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Travel, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - UNESCO United Fund Campaign, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - University Allocations and Positions - Administration, Research Co-op Education, Graduate Office, Students, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - University Allocations and Positions - College of Agriculture, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - University Allocations and Positions - College of Architecture, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - University Allocations and Positions - College of Arts and Sciences, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - University Allocations and Positions - College of Business, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - University Allocations and Positions - College of Engineering, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - University Allocations and Positions - College of Home Economics, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - University Allocations and Positions - Extension, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - University Allocations and Positions - Library, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - University Allocations and Positions Recapitulation, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - University Bookstore, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - University Committees - Nominations and Elections, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - University Council Constitution, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Agenda items
    - University Development, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Building dedications
    - University Services, H.W. Swink, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - MA program in Economics in Reston
    - Vice Presidents (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 31, Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Vice President for Administration
      - Vice President for Executive
      - Vice President for Economics
    - Vice President of Student Affairs (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
    - Virginia Associated Research Center (VARC), 1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Virginia College Association, Virginia Academy of Science, and Virginia Junior Academy of Science, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - VPI Centennial, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - VPI Educational Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Psychological Association, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Visiting Scientists Research Associateships, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Who's Who, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Work-Study Program, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - YMCA, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Series VIII: Records and Correspondence, 1970-1971
  - "A's" Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs and Staff Meetings and Academic Advising, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Academic Calendar Questionnaires, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Academic Year, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Pros and cons of quarters and semesters
  - Ad Hoc Committee for Interdisciplinary Study, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Fall Administration Conference, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Intern Appointments, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Intern - Julio Lopez, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Interns Prior to July 1, 1971, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Admissions, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Admissions, Correspondence (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 24-25)
  - Agriculture, College of, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Agriculture, College of - Space, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Association, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - American Association of Higher Education, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - College and university bulletins
  - AAUP - AAUW, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - American Association of University Professors reports
  - American Board of Expansion in Professional Psychology, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - American Council on Education, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Anatomy, Agriculture, Anaerobic - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report - President, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - American Society for Engineering Education, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Architecture, College of, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Architecture, College of - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Architecture, College of - Space, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Arts and Sciences Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Association, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Association, Athletic Program, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Baily Research Trust, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Biochemistry, Nutrition, Dairy Sciences and Animal Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Black Students - Black Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Board of Visitors, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Bookkeeping Allotment, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Bookkeeping Central Store Charges, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Book Keeper Ledgers, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Bookkeeping Ledgers, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Bookkeeping Print Shop, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Bookkeeping Supplies, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Bookkeeping Telephone, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Bookkeeping Travel, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Building Projections, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Building Committee (2 folders), 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 26-27)
  - Business, Correspondence (4 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 28-31)
  - Arts and Sciences Chairman's Meetings Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Business Administration Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - "C's" Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Campus Bookstore, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Catalogue Committee, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Centennial, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - CEC - Dr. Heckle, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - CEC, Payroll, Repairs, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Center for Environmental Studies (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Chemistry and Biology Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Bruce Parker's "Life in the Clouds" article
  - Collegiate Times, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Commandments of Cadets, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Selection of band director
  - Commencement Committee, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Commission on Student Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 14-15)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies (2 folders), 1971 (Box 17, Folder 16-17)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies - Academic Appeals Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies - Subcommittees I, II, III, IV, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Committee College System, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Committee, Letterhead, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Interdisciplinary Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Committee, Principles of Economics, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Computer Center (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
  - Computer Science - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Consulting (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 27-28)
  - Consulting - Approval from Dr. McKeefery, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Cooperative Education Program (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 30-31)
  - Copying Center, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Off Campus, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Council of Deans, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Counseling Center - Dr. Cook, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Curriculum Revisions, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Deans, Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Deans, Meetings with Dr. Malpass, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Deans' Meetings - Miscellaneous (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
    - Faculty members' responsibilities at times of disruption
    - Public utterances by faculty
    - Computer Center
    - Report Regarding Moratorium, 1971-05-05
    - Faculty Survey of Student Opinions
    - Faculty Advising
    - Faculty appointments, promotions, and tenure
    - Roles and responsibilities of department heads
    - Interviews with graduating black students
  - Deans' Meetings - "Counter Orientation" (Box 18, Folder 6A)
  - Degrees, Joint College Conferral of 1971, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Departmental Visits - Dr. Hahn, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Disadvantaged Students, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Disciplinary Action, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Economics 221 (2 folders), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
  - Economics, Department of - Dr. Darton, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Education 498 - Higher Education, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Education, College of - Correspondence (4 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 16-19)
  - Education, College of - Space, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Education, Higher - Compact Survey, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Education for High Risk Students, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Employment Offers and Biographical Data Sheets (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 23-24)
  - Employment Offers and Historical Data Sheets, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Employment Offers and Vitae (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
  - Engineering, College of, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Engineering, College of - Correspondence (4 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 4-7)
  - Engineering Mechanics and Fundamentals, Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Engineering Mining Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Engineering - Nuclear, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Engineering Technological Program, Proposed, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - English, Department of - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Information on the Humanities and student revolt
  - English Speaking Union, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Enrollment Statistics and Projection, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Extension and 4-H Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Executive Vice President, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Extension Division Correspondence (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
  - Extension Division and Graduate School, Reston Campus (2 folders), 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 20-21)
  - Faculty Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Faculty, College of Business, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Evaluation, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Exchange Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Orientation Program, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate and Titles, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Survey, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Work Load - Annual Report of Engineering, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Fellowships, Special Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Food Science, Technology and Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Languages Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Forestry and Wildlife Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Foundations, Scholarship Program et., 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fraternity-Sorority Program, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Furniture Orders, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - General Counsel, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Report on student freedom of expression in campus newspaper
  - Geological Sciences - Development Proposal, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Geology, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Gifts, Loans, Foundation Funds, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Glee Club - Kingma, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Graduate School, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Graduate Students, Graduate School, Graduate Academy Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Graduate Studies Questionnaire on Standards and Criteria for Graduate Instruction, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - GTA, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Grants, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Hahn, TM Jr. Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Home Economics, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Home Economics - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Human Nutrition and Food - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - IAESTE, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Information Services, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Institute of International Education, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Office of Institutional Research, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Inter-American Institute of Ecology, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - International Studies Curriculum, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Internship Students, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - The John Marshall Hotel, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Law Enforcement Consortium, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Law Enforcement Education Program, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Learning Resources Center, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Leave - Education, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)